

Victor Andre

Goudschaal Ingold

victorgou.design@gmail.com Montevideo, Uruguay. 098 449 788

LANGUAGE

Spanish (native) English (native speaker)

SUMMARY STATEMENT

Front-end Developer & Designer with 4 years of experience creating digital products such as web-landings, web-applications, branding manuals and more. I strive to constantly keep learning about technology to expand my capabilities as a digital creator. I recommend checking out my web-portfolio.

CORE QUALIFICATION

Dedicated and
Organized.
Very Curious and
Motivated.

Adaptable self-taught learner.

DEV TOOLS

HTML & CSS
Javascript
React.js

ART TOOLS

Python

Adobe Suite Figma Rhino 3D V-ray Ableton

EXPERIENCE

(2023 - 2024) Frontend Developer for the Skygpu.net development team. Skygpu.net is a platform that offers decentralized AI tools built on top of the Antelope blockchain stack. I recently created their "terminal" Landing-page, check it out as an example.

(2021 - 2022) Art Director at OmbuOmbu.

OmbuOmbu offers Branding and Marketing services. My job was to directly assess clients, defining and maintaining the project's alignments and the client satisfaction. Landing-page

(2020 - 2023) Freelancer.

Projects and assignments for a variety of clients have given me experience on design, development and the power of adaptability.

(2019) Graphic Designer at Reinventar.

Reinventar offers laser engraving services and billboard production.

FORMATION

Born in 1999 in Uruguay, Traveled to NewYork a month old and lived there until 2006 having fluency in both languages.

In 2017 graduated bachelor's degree of Architecture in Montevideo Liceo 10.

In 2018 started studying in FADU UDELAR (University of Architecture, Design and Urbanism) for 3 years, developing a hard interest and knowledge on design process and art direction.

Since 2020 self taught constantly expanding my knowledge in the field of art and technology through work assignments and experimental projects.